Abdulrahman Alsuhaibi

Riyadh, Saudi Arabia

alsuhaibiabdulrahman@gmail.com

+967775474720

linkedin.com/in/alsuhaibi96

https://baaeed.com/u/alsuhaibi01

Summary

Experienced Full Stack Web Developer, adept in all stages of web development. Knowledgeable in FinTech Systems, restful API, user interface, CMS websites, and Creating Portfolios. Equipped with a diverse and promising skill-set. including HTML5,CSS3, PHP, JS, TS, Java, and SQL.

Frameworks like: Laravel, Angular, Node.Js and Frappe. Able to effectively manage other team members during building projects, as well as collaborate in a team setting.

Experience

△ Full Stack Developer

أجير Ajeer

Mar 2023 - Present (1 year 1 month)

Working with ajeer team on building software solutions and maintaining web applications.

Tech Stack:

Front-end:Vue.js,nuxt.js,html.css,js

Back-end:laravel php

Tools:vs code ,tableplus, jira,postman

Database:mysql

Deployment:GitHub action

Frontend Developer

FinTechSys

Jul 2022 - Present (1 year 9 months)

Working with finTech team on building financial software solutions and maintaining web applications.

Tech Stack:

Front-end:Vue.js,nuxt.js,html.css,js,bootstrap,tailwindcss

Back-end:frappe

Tools:vs code ,github project management board,postman

Database:mysql

Deployment: GitHub actions

Web Application Developer

Jun 2021 - Present (2 years 10 months)

Planned, Designed, developed, deployed, and maintained web applications.

Helped in improving ideas by 80%.

Worked well independently and in teams that consists of 2 or more.

Used different technology stacks like: WordPress, Laravel PHP framework and Agile Methodologies.

Web Application Developer

AZ Software

Nov 2021 - Dec 2021 (2 months)

Managed front-end and development of the company's Portfolio (The first portfolio).

Helped to analyze and build database for some mobile applications (90% of the company's work).

Became knowledgeable in new standards, technologies, and trends in website development.

Full Stack Developer

E pulse cart

Oct 2021 - Nov 2021 (2 months)

Designed, Helped and maintained front-end websites by 90%.

Helped to analyze and build applications with other teams (more than 5 developers).

English Teacher

Canadian Center

Sep 2018 - Aug 2021 (3 years)

Helped, trained, inspired the Center Students in learning English as a second language.

Taught, trained and managed advanced English courses of 15 and more students.

Helped the students to improve their speaking skills by 50%.

Education

Coding Academy

Bootcamp Certificate, Full-stack Development

Jan 2022 - May 2022

Graduated with high honor and a large stack of technologies and programming languages.

Lead and Helped other team members.

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science

Aug 2017 - Aug 2021

Graduated with 87% of score and was one of the best 5 students.

Learnt a large set of methodologies and concepts in programming.

Technical Institute

Diploma of Education, Computer Programming

Oct 2015 - Sep 2017

Studied a large set of programming languages and started to love coding back then.

Hikma University Center (HUC)

Dilploma, English

Sep 2015 - Aug 2016

Chosen as one of the best 5 students who completed the diploma.

Learnt English language and used it in real conversations.

Licenses & Certifications

Time Management: Working from Home - LinkedIn

Cisco Network Programmability Engineer Specialist - Cisco

International Computer Drivers License (ICDL,)

Full -Stack Developer -Bootcamp

Issued Jan 2022 - Expires May 2022

Best Speaker in English - Hikma University Center

Skills

Nuxt.js • Linux • User Experience Design (UED) • Vue.js • API Development • Front-End Development • Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) • Client Requirements • Version Control • Software Development

Honors & Awards

A thanking Certificate - Kamal Baghzah

Apr 2021

As a part of the reward, I participated in the competition of the best speaker in the Canadian Center. I helped in making the students speak English as their second language.

I also trained a large number of students that can be 15 or more.